<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Tiago Andres Vaz: Professional Portfolio in Computer Science and Healthcare</title>
        <link>https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/</link>
        <description>Professional portfolio in healthcare software development</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:57:40 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Experience and Projects Done</title>
    <link>https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/experience/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:57:40 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/experience/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[During Covid-19 pandemics I had to compile my work as a Computer Scientist. To share it with other people around the world in projects that I am (or might be) involved.
I hope that my readers here, are also creating amazing software!
Special Motivation  I have built this website to learn Hugo (a very nice static website creator coded using &ldquo;Go&rdquo;). This site is published at github.io, a free place to host web content like this!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Academic and Executive Education</title>
    <link>https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/education/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 21:57:40 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://tiagoandresvaz.github.io/education/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Motivation
Since high school times I am coding and thinking software to solve problems. There is always a page in blank&hellip;
Culture
My family culture believes that investing in education is the path to follow with confidence and altitude in your professional career. So, I have tracked both academic and executive education accomplishments.
Here you will find:
Academic Titles   Bachelor in Computer Science - PUC-RS (Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Rio Grande do Sul): 1995-2002]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
